<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Incompleteness</title>
  <link href="http://incompleteness.me/mozblog/atom.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="http://incompleteness.me/blog" />
  <updated>2011-12-16T12:22:33+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://incompleteness.me/</id>
  <author><name>Joe Walker</name></author>

  <entry>
    <title>Firefox Command Line Hackathon</title>
    <link href="http://incompleteness.me/blog/2012/06/20/command-line-hackathon/" />
    <updated>2012-06-20T12:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://incompleteness.me/blog/2012/06/20/command-line-hackathon/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: On June 27th, the Firefox developer tools team is holding a hackathon to
add to the list of commands for the Firefox developers toolbar.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/donotlick/5272510170/sizes/l/in/photostream/"&gt;
    &lt;img src="http://incompleteness.me/images/posts/hackathon1.jpg" alt="people hacking" /&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p&gt;See this recent &lt;a href="http://incompleteness.me/blog/2012/06/18/firefox-command-line/"&gt;blog post for context on the new developers command line&lt;/a&gt;.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm in the process of finishing off &lt;a href="https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=724055"&gt;bug 724055&lt;/a&gt; which will make it as
easy as is possible to create new commands, just set a pref to point to a
directory where your commands are stored in JSON (ish) files, and you're done.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the next few days I'll update this post with a set of resources for creating
commands and ideas for commands. We'll hang out in IRC and crank away and see
how many commands we can get written in a day.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you can spare some time, we'd love to have some help.

&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry><entry>
    <title>Firefox Command Line for Developers</title>
    <link href="http://incompleteness.me/blog/2012/06/18/firefox-command-line/" />
    <updated>2012-06-18T12:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://incompleteness.me/blog/2012/06/18/firefox-command-line/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: We're adding a toolbar to Firefox, for developers, which includes a
command line.
It's a great place to add small tools and experimental features, and we're
making it easy to add your own commands.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The toolbar should land in Firefox 16 or 17 and will look like this:

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div style="overflow-x: hidden;"&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://incompleteness.me/images/posts/gcli-look-mac.png" alt="GCLI on a Mac" /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The buttons are useful, but I'm most excited about the commands.
We can add an almost unlimited set of commands here without cluttering up the
UI, or making things slow, and we've done lots of work to make the command line
easy to use.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The challenge: It might be stretching things a little to call the command line
a 'platform', and commands 'apps', but the command line still needs commands to
be successful. There's a list of commands that we're working on for
manipulating Firefox developer tools, and we'll be expanding this list to
include system level commands too.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're planning on a hackathon in a couple of weeks to add to the list of
commands and to check that it really as as easy as we think it is to extend.
Details soon.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to try it out, it's in Nightly now, you'll need to flip the
&lt;code&gt;devtools.toolbar.enable&lt;/code&gt; preference in &lt;code&gt;about:config&lt;/code&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>

</feed>
